<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?><items> 
<item> 
<title>Nor&#039;wester Restaurant Cafe & Bar</title> 
<image>/assets/images/7502_21_03_09_Nor__Wester_Restaurant_Cafe___Bar.jpg</image> 
<image2>/assets/images/7503_27_11_19_norwester2_jpg.jpg</image2> 
<image3></image3> <image4></image4> <logo></logo> <address1>95 Main North Road</address1> 
<address2>Amberley</address2> 
<phone>+64 3 314 9411 </phone> 
<fax></fax> 
<mobile>Moblie</mobile> 
<freephone></freephone> 
<email>info@norwestercafe.co.nz</email> 
<web>www.norwestercafe.co.nz</web> 
<desc> On the main road in the heart of Amberley, the popular Nor&#039;Wester serves locals, travellers and visitors from all around the globe, with fresh inspiring menus, fine wine from Waipara Valley and beyond, as well as pouring some of the best coffee you&#039;ll find in New Zealand. 

Established in 1997, this locally owned restaurant is seasoned and delivers a sophisticated experience, underpinned by wholesome values. 
The renovated 1928 bungalow houses inviting dining spaces, an open fire and provides a loved workspace for the 17 dedicated staff that is committed to cookery and beverage service.  

Bookings for dining advised.

Open every day from 9am breakfast, lunch and dinner.</desc> 
</item> 
<item> 
<title>The Paddock Cafe</title> 
<image>/assets/images/noimage.jpg</image> <image2></image2> <image3></image3> <image4></image4> <logo></logo> <address1>8 Hall Street</address1> 
<address2>Cheviot</address2> 
<phone>+64 3 319 8430</phone> 
<fax></fax> 
<mobile>Moblie</mobile> 
<freephone></freephone> 
<email></email> 
<web></web> 
<desc>A must stop, serving great coffee all day. A great selection of tempting honest home-made food which is made on-site. Gluten-free options available. Plenty of off-street parking. 

Open 7 days.</desc> 
</item> 
<item> 
<title>Two Rivers Gallery Cafe</title> 
<image>/assets/images/6702_21_02_48_TWO_RIVERS_GALLERY_CAFE.jpg</image> 
<image2></image2> <image3></image3> <image4></image4> <logo></logo> <address1>11 Hall Street</address1> 
<address2>Cheviot</address2> 
<phone>+64 3 319 8505</phone> 
<fax></fax> 
<mobile>Moblie</mobile> 
<freephone></freephone> 
<email>ask@tworiverscafe.co.nz</email> 
<web>www.tworiverscafe.co.nz</web> 
<desc>Situated mid way between Christchurch & Kaikoura on State Highway 1, Two Rivers Cafe in Cheviot is the ideal stop for breakfast, lunch or coffee and a snack. The food is all made in-house, there are daily specials and a fine selection of local wines and beer. 

The cafe runs in conjunction with a wonderful modern art gallery and offers a relaxed atmosphere, friendly service and both indoor and outdoor eating areas.

Open 7 days a week and occasionally for evening dining.</desc> 
</item> 
</items> 
