<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?><items> 
<item> 
<title>Heritage Hanmer Springs</title> 
<image>/assets/images/2202_20_04_50_HERITAGE_HANMER_SPRINGS.jpg</image> 
<image2>/assets/images/2202_20_04_52_HERITAGE_HANMER_SPRINGS.jpg</image2> 
<image3>/assets/images/2203_27_10_43_heritage3_jpg.jpg</image3> 
<image4></image4> <logo></logo> <address1>1 Conical Hill Road (PO Box 10)</address1> 
<address2>Hanmer Springs</address2> 
<phone>+64 3 315 0060</phone> 
<fax></fax> 
<mobile>Moblie</mobile> 
<freephone>0800 738 732</freephone> 
<email>res.heritagezhp@heritagehotels.co.nz</email> 
<web>www.heritagehotels.co.nz</web> 
<desc>Adventure or relaxation - Hanmer Springs has it all! 

A glorious alpine setting just  90-minutes&#039; drive north of Christchurch makes Hanmer Springs the perfect alpine escape.

The landmark hotel Heritage Hanmer Springs is the only fully-serviced hotel in Hanmer Springs, situated across the road from the famous Thermal Pools & Spa. 

Set in 9 acres of delightfully landscaped grounds, the hotel provides well-appointed rooms, garden rooms and self-contained 3-bedroom villas.

The extensive hotel grounds include a number of 3-bedroom Villas offering their own garage, self-contained kitchen and laundry facilities together with an open plan dining and living area. There are also rooms set amongst the gardens offering their own outdoor area and plentiful complimentary  car parking.

Guests can choose to dine in the grand Isobel&#039;s Restaurant with its large windows overlooking the landscaped grounds or alfresco on the broad, sunny terrace. Relax and de-stress in the outdoor swimming pool, tennis & petanque courts or in the lounge bar with open-fire. 

- Centrally located in Hanmer Springs township
- Range of accommodation options to suit couples, families or groups
- Fully self-contained 3-bedroom villas include full kitchen, dining and lounge areas plus internal access garage
- Restaurant and bar, swimming pool, 
	tennis court and petanque court
- Gazebo and outdoor area perfect for weddings</desc> 
</item> 
<item> 
<title>Select Braemar Lodge & Spa </title> 
<image>/assets/images/2602_21_09_12_SELECT_BRAEMAR_LODGE___SPA_.jpg</image> 
<image2></image2> <image3></image3> <image4></image4> <logo></logo> <address1>283 Medway Road</address1> 
<address2>Hanmer Springs</address2> 
<phone>+64 3 315 7555</phone> 
<fax></fax> 
<mobile>Moblie</mobile> 
<freephone></freephone> 
<email>enquiries@selectbraemarlodge.com</email> 
<web> www.selectbraemarlodge.co.nz</web> 
<desc>Offering the largest suites in the village, with floor to ceiling windows and doors that open to a private balcony (some with outdoor Jacuzzi) and spectacular views over the Hanmer Basin and mountains. 

Each suite has a super king-size bed, gas fire, LCD flat screen TV, ipod sound system, large elegant bathroom with 
spa bath and double shower. 

Free wireless internet. 

Day Spa, Restaurant and Bar.</desc> 
</item> 
</items> 
