<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?><items> 
<item> 
<title>Waipara Valley Farmers Market</title> 
<image>/assets/images/7802_21_03_15_Waipara_Valley_Farmers_Market.jpg</image> 
<image2></image2> <image3></image3> <image4></image4> <logo></logo> <address1>66 Carters Road (Outside Hurunui District Council Chambers)</address1> 
<address2>Amberley</address2> 
<phone>0064 21833571 </phone> 
<fax></fax> 
<mobile>Moblie</mobile> 
<freephone></freephone> 
<email>waiparavalleyfm@gmail.com</email> 
<web></web> 
<desc>Every Saturday: 9am - 12noon.
Throughout the year.

Visit the Waipara Valley Farmers Market for award winning food from local growers and producers.

Find us on Facebook.</desc> 
</item> 
<item> 
<title>Waipara Vintage Festival</title> 
<image>/assets/images/10603_18_09_44_WAIPARA_VINTAGE_FESTIVAL.jpg</image> 
<image2></image2> <image3></image3> <image4></image4> <logo></logo> <address1></address1> 
<address2>Waipara</address2> 
<phone>0064 3  314 6813</phone> 
<fax></fax> 
<mobile>Moblie</mobile> 
<freephone></freephone> 
<email>www.waiparavintagefestival.com</email> 
<web></web> 
<desc>Dates: 01 SEPTEMBER 2013
exact dates to be confirmed
Location: Waipara
Venue: Mackenzies Road, Waipara

Day for all that is vintage... a fun 2 day event for all ages.

The Weka Pass Railway runs steam train rides from a temporary &#039;halt&#039; for the Festival adjacent to the festival site.

With over 100 vintage tractors, headers, trucks and machinery of yester-year on display over the two days, making it a great family outing to admire and respect agricultural progress, through the preservation of various machinery and the way farming has changed over the years.

A double decker bus and Unimog will be providing rides around the festival and there will also be a live Action military display and WWII Search light.

A display of farm animals, lambs, puppies, hens, along with a sheep shearing display will highlight everyday farming activities.

A wide variety of stalls selling art and craft items and hot food stalls are all on the grounds.

Plenty of toilets and we have free parking for everyone, EFTPOS will be available for gate entry.

Proceeds from the Festival will aid in the of restoration of the Glenmark Church which was damaged after Canterbury&#039;s recent earthquakes.

Keep an eye on www.waiparavintagefestival.com for updated information.

Cost: 	adults $12, children $5, pre-schoolers free

Gates sales only
</desc> 
</item> 
</items> 
